[{"answer": "We didn't say that", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Millennium.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "...we couldn't say that we said it", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "We couldn't say that, because even if we did..", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Millennium.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "You see what we're saying", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Lemme just check my messages.  Maybe a nicer girl called. my friend presses the '07' button, without looking", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Millennium.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Hello? Who's this", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Sorry I'm late, but look what I found in the Yankee Hall of Pride display case", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Millennium.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Is it?  my friend looks disturbed by my friend's actions", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " You knew I was having a millennium party, but you just had to throw yours on the same day", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Millennium.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Yeah, well you're gonna have to cancel it, because I've told everybody about my party", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Aw, come on there now", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Millennium.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Nonsense. You do everything wrong", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "No, no, no no, listen to me. I work in fashion. Together, we can drive that place outta business and make Cinqo de Mayo numero uno... de Mayo. my friend comes out behind the counter", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Millennium.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " You? What're you doing here", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " You? What're you doing here", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Millennium.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "No you don't. You own that place. Unless you own both stores.", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " What", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Millennium.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I don't know, my friend. That doesn't sound..", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Hello my friend.  What did you say to my friend? I just got her cancellation in the mail", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Millennium.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Well, it's her mistake. Because she is going to miss the party of a lifetime", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Hello", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Millennium.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "It's my friend. Who's this", "qsentId": 22}]